[ { "voc": { "voc_id": "10", "question": "Pron", "list_id": "7" }, "answer": { "answer_id": "7", "voc_id": "10", "answer": "ich", "multi_choice": "0" }, "user_data": { "answer_id": "7", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" }, "complete": { "voc_id": "10", "question": "Pron", "list_id": "7", "answer_id": "7", "answer": "ich", "multi_choice": "0", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" } }, { "voc": { "voc_id": "10", "question": "Pron", "list_id": "7" }, "answer": { "answer_id": "8", "voc_id": "10", "answer": "du", "multi_choice": "0" }, "user_data": { "answer_id": "8", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" }, "complete": { "voc_id": "10", "question": "Pron", "list_id": "7", "answer_id": "8", "answer": "du", "multi_choice": "0", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" } }, { "voc": { "voc_id": "10", "question": "Pron", "list_id": "7" }, "answer": { "answer_id": "9", "voc_id": "10", "answer": "er", "multi_choice": "0" }, "user_data": { "answer_id": "9", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" }, "complete": { "voc_id": "10", "question": "Pron", "list_id": "7", "answer_id": "9", "answer": "er", "multi_choice": "0", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" } }, { "voc": { "voc_id": "11", "question": "eins", "list_id": "7" }, "answer": { "answer_id": "10", "voc_id": "11", "answer": "one", "multi_choice": "0" }, "user_data": { "answer_id": "10", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" }, "complete": { "voc_id": "11", "question": "eins", "list_id": "7", "answer_id": "10", "answer": "one", "multi_choice": "0", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" } }, { "voc": { "voc_id": "12", "question": "zwei", "list_id": "7" }, "answer": { "answer_id": "11", "voc_id": "12", "answer": "two", "multi_choice": "0" }, "user_data": { "answer_id": "11", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" }, "complete": { "voc_id": "12", "question": "zwei", "list_id": "7", "answer_id": "11", "answer": "two", "multi_choice": "0", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" } }, { "voc": { "voc_id": "13", "question": "drei", "list_id": "7" }, "answer": { "answer_id": "12", "voc_id": "13", "answer": "three", "multi_choice": "0" }, "user_data": { "answer_id": "12", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" }, "complete": { "voc_id": "13", "question": "drei", "list_id": "7", "answer_id": "12", "answer": "three", "multi_choice": "0", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" } }, { "voc": { "voc_id": "14", "question": "vier", "list_id": "7" }, "answer": { "answer_id": "13", "voc_id": "14", "answer": "four", "multi_choice": "0" }, "user_data": { "answer_id": "13", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" }, "complete": { "voc_id": "14", "question": "vier", "list_id": "7", "answer_id": "13", "answer": "four", "multi_choice": "0", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" } }, { "voc": { "voc_id": "15", "question": "fünf", "list_id": "7" }, "answer": { "answer_id": "14", "voc_id": "15", "answer": "five", "multi_choice": "0" }, "user_data": { "answer_id": "14", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" }, "complete": { "voc_id": "15", "question": "fünf", "list_id": "7", "answer_id": "14", "answer": "five", "multi_choice": "0", "right": "0", "wrong": "0", "rating": "-1" } } ]